<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>my project</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on my project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>my post</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/m/</guid>
      <description>##Here is my post
#Using R studio and Python together is fun Does the names Python and R next to next other sound scary? That is what I thought when I first heard them together but, the more I leaned about them the easier it got. Each of them have their own special features and being able to use them together makes things better. 
library(reticulate) something &amp;lt;-&amp;quot;This is my name:&amp;quot; ag&amp;lt;- &amp;quot;My age is&amp;quot; first=&amp;quot;sarina&amp;quot; last=&amp;quot;Khajeharzani&amp;quot; age=20+3 print(r.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project2 Sarina</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>My project 2 ##Introduction For this project I am using the bechdel data from the fivethirtyeight. This data is about the Dollar-And-Cents Case Against Hollywood’s Exclusion of Women to see different information about the Hollywood movies that have a female actress who is the main character to see if woman are excluded from movies or not. Some of the most important factors of this data are the year, test (indicating the type of the test that they used), the budget of the movie, Binary which says that the movie passes the test or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sarina project1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>knitr::opts_chunk$set(echo = TRUE) My project 1  introduction: I choose the two data sets (hate_crimes) and (state_info) from the database fivethirtyeight. Both of my datasets have the states name in common and that is how I joined them. I moved to the U.S. about four years ago and I always wanted to learn more about it. The data set state_info has the variables: states name, abbreviations of the states, divion and region of each state.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
